Guide to the National Religious Partnership for the Environment Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Partner Organizations, 1990-2009; Series II
  - National Council of Churches of Christ in the U.S.A.
    - Campaigns and events
      - NRPE General Assembly, the Regeneration Project, global climate change campaigns, 2000–2002 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Publicity and outreach
      - Press lists, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Press lists, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Press coverage, 1996–1999 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Program materials
      - Training booklet, scholarship, 1990s (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Pamphlets, scholarship, 1990s (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Pamphlets, scholarship, 2000s (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - United States Conference of Catholic Bishops
    - Organization and policy records
      - Administrative materials part 1 - includes meeting agendas, budgets, job descriptions, memorandum, correspondence, grant proposals, initiatives, newsletters, 1990s (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Administrative materials part 2 - includes meeting agendas, budgets, job descriptions, memorandum, correspondence, grant proposals, initiatives, newsletters, 1990s (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Administrative materials part 3 - includes meeting agendas, budgets, job descriptions, memorandum, correspondence, grant proposals, initiatives, newsletters, event materials, 1990s (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Administrative materials part 4 - includes meeting agendas, budgets, job descriptions, memorandum, correspondence, grant proposals, initiatives, newsletters, event materials, 2000s (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Administrative materials part 5 - includes meeting agendas, budgets, job descriptions, memorandum, correspondence, grant proposals, initiatives, newsletters, event materials, 2000s (Box 28, Folder 4)
        Global Climate Change: A Plea for Dialogue, Prudence, and the Common Good
      - Catholic Small Grants, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Campaigns and events
      - United States Catholic Conference part 1, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - United States Catholic Conference part 2, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Climate Change, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Children's Environmental Health part 1, 2000s (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Children's Environmental Health part 2, 2000s (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Children's Environmental Health part 3, 2000s (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Children's Environmental Health part 4, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 4)
        Training materials
      - Children's Environmental Health part 5, 2001–2004 (Box 29, Folder 5)
        Information on video
      - Children's Environmental Health part 6, 2000s (Box 29, Folder 6)
        Correspondence
      - Children's Environmental Health part 7, 2000s (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - Children's Environmental Health part 8, 2000s (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - What Would Jesus Do? part 1, 2002–2003 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - What Would Jesus Do? part 2, 2002–2003 (Box 30, Folder 3)
        News articles
      - Environmental Justice part 1, 1993–2003 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Environmental Justice part 2, 1993–2003 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Healthcare Without Harm, 1996–1998 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Health Track, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Catholic Conference, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous, 1990–2004 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Publicity and outreach
      - Press coverage and newsletters, 1999–2009 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Program materials
      - Brochures, pamphlets and scholarship, 1990s (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Brochures, pamphlets and scholarship, 1990s (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Brochures, pamphlets and scholarship, 1990s (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Brochures, pamphlets and scholarship, 2000s (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Brochures, pamphlets and scholarship, 2000s (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Resource Materials, 1987-2012; Series III
  - Related organizations
    - American Public Health Association, 2008 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Apollo Project, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - American Jewish Committee, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Aspen Institute, 2001–2006 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Benedictine Women of Madison, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Biodiversity Project part 1, 1998–2001 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Biodiversity Project part 2, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Biodiversity Project part 3, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Black Church Environmental Justice Network, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Boston Theological Institute, 1990s (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Canfei Nasharim, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - California Interfaith Power and Light, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Cathedral Church of Saint John part 1, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Cathedral Church of Saint John, 1989–1990 (Box 32, Folder 14)
      Includes "Program for Environment - City & Planet"
    - Catholic Coalition for Children, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Catholic Coalition on Climate Change, 2009 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Center for Children's Health, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Center for the Respect of Life and the Environment, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Christian Life Commission, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Christian Society for the Green Cross, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 19a)
      Issue of Green Cross on Endangered Species
    - Church of the Brethren, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Climate Protection Initiative, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Columbia Earth Institute, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Commission on Religion in Appalachia, 1999–2000 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Concern, Inc., 1987–1991 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Consultative Group on Biodiversity, 1990–1999 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Defense of the Wildlife, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Department of Education, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Earth Charter Project, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Earth Keeping Ministries, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Earth Ministry part 1, 1993–2009 (Box 32, Folder 30)
      Newsletters
    - Earth Ministry part 2, 1996–1997 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Earth Ministry part 3, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Earth Score, 1993–2006 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Eco America, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Eco Church, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Ecumenical Ministries, 2003–2009 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Educational Ministries, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Energy Fund Coalition, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Environmental Action Coalition, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Environment Committee of the Peace Commission, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Environmental Defense, 1996–2007 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Environmental Frontlines, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Environmental Information Center, 1995–1996 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Environmental Justice Resource Center, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Environmental Protection Agency part 1, 1991–1993 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Environmental Protection Agency part 2, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Environmental Protection Center, 1992–1995 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Environmental Task Force, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Episcopal Bishops of New England, 2000s (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Episcopal Diocese of Pennsylvania, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Fenton Communications, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Fetzer Institute, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Garrison Institute, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Georgetown Environmental Law Institute, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Goldman Environmental, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Green Group, 2004–2006 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Harwood Group, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Hedgegrow Habitat, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Heinz Family Foundation, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Institute for Ecology, Justice, and Faith, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - John Ray Inititative, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Joint Appeal by Religion and Science for the Environment - 1, 1990–1992 (Box 33, Folder 22)
      See also the Union for Concerned Scientists
    - Joint Appeal by Religion and Science for the Environment - 2, 1991–1997 (Box 33, Folder 23)
      See also Union for Concerned Scientists
    - Joint Appeal by Religion and Science for the Environment - 3, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Joint Project and Clean Water Fund, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Judith Helfand Productions Inc., 1997 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Justice for Animals Fund, 2000s (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Just Transportation, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - League of Conservation Voters, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Lutheran School of Theology in Chicago, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Millennial Ecosystem Assessment, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Ministry of God's Creation, 2000s (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Mount Gilead Baptist Church, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - National Association of Evangelicals, 2000s (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - National Commission on Energy, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - National Environmental Trust, 1998–1999 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - National Resources Defense Council, 2001–2003 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - National Wildlife Federation, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - New York Department of Health, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Nicholas Institute for Environmental Policy Solutions, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - North American Conference on Christianity and Ecology, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 41a)
      "Discerning the Signs of These Times" - A Congress of Earthkeeping Ministries
    - Nuclear Waste Citizens Coalition, 1996–1997 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Omega Institute for Holistic Studies, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - PEW Center for Charitable Trusts part 1, 2003–2012 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - PEW Center for Charitable Trusts part 2, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Presbyterian Church part 1, 1990–2004 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Presbyterian Church part 2, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Presbyterian Church part 3, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - President's Council on Sustainable Development part 1, 1993–1995 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - President's Council on Sustainable Development, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Rabbinical Assembly, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Religion Newswriter's Association, 1990–2004 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Roundtable Associates, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Sacred Heart League, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Scenic America, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Seminar on Jesus Spirituality, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Servant Leadership School, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Sierra Club, 1998–2006 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Tarrance Group, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Texas Impact, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Time Magazine, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - 20/20, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Union of Concerned Scientists part 1, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Union of Concerned Scientists part 2, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Union of Concerned Scientists part 3, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Union of Concerned Scientists, 1995–1996 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - United Jewish Organization, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 22a)
      The Activist's Handbook
    - United Nations Environmental Program, 2001–2009 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - United States Department of Agriculture, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - United States Global Change Research Program, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - United States PIRG, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - University of Virginia's Institute for Environmental Negotiation, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Watch Tower Society, 1994–2005 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - White House Climate Change Task Force, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Woodstock Foundation, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - World Business Council for Sustainable Development, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - World Council of Churches, 1997–2006 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - World Energy Assessment, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - World Resources Institute part 1, 2000–2002 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - World Resources Institute part 2, 1994–2004 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - World Wildlife Fund, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Yale Divinity School, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Yale School of Forestry and Environmental Studies part 1, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Yale School of Forestry and Environmental Studies part 2, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Individuals
    - Bakken, Peter, 2003–2004 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Ball, Jim, 1998–2006 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Decanio, Stephen J., 1997 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Fromherz, Frank, 1998–1999 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Hamilton, Dave, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Hart, John, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Himes, Kenneth R., 1998 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Jenkins, Christine L., 1993 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Landrigan, Philip J., 2005 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Lubchenco, Jane, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Pope, Carl, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Rasmussen, Larry, 1995–1996 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Rockefeller, Steven, 1996–1999 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Sen, Amartya, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Sheldon, Joseph K., 2004 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Smith, Angela M., 2006 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Troster, Larry, 2002–2004 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Tucker, Mary Evelyn, 1996–1998 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Wirth, Timothy E., 1994–1995 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - News clippings
    - Chronological sequence, 1994 January-November (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Chronological sequence, 1995 January-December (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Chronological sequence, 1996 January-December (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Chronological sequence, 1997 January-February (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Chronological sequence, 1997 March-December (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Chronological sequence, 1998 January-December (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Chronological sequence, 1999 February-October (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Chronological sequence, 1999 November-December (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Chronological sequence, 2000 January-June (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Chronological sequence, 2000 July-November (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Chronological sequence, 2001 January-June (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Chronological sequence, 2001 July-December (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Chronological sequence, 2002 January-October (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Chronological sequence part 1, 2002 November (Box 35, Folder 34)
      What Would Jesus Drive
    - Chronological sequence part 2, 2002 November (Box 36, Folder 1)
      Related Materials
    - Chronological sequence part 3, 2002 November (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Chronological sequence, 2002 December (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Chronological sequence, 2003 January-November (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Chronological sequence, 2004 January-July (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Chronological sequence, 2004 August-December (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Chronological sequence, 2005 January-July (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Chronological sequence, 2005 August-October (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Chronological sequence, 2005 November-December (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Chronological sequence, 2006 January-April (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Chronological sequence, 2006 May (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Chronological sequence, 2006 June-September (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Chronological sequence, 2006 October (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Chronological sequence, 2006 November (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Chronological sequence, 2006 December (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Chronological sequence, 2007 January (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Chronological sequence, 2007 February-March (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Chronological sequence, 2007 April (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Chronological sequence, 2007 May-October (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Chronological sequence, 2008 March (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Press service clippings, 1990–1994 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Press service clippings, 1995 January-May (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Press service clippings, 1995 June-December (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Press service clippings, 1996 March-July (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Press service clippings, 1996 August-December (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Press service clippings, 1997 January-May (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Press service clippings, 1997 June-November (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Press service clippings, 1998 January-June (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Press service clippings, 1998 July-November (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Press service clippings, 1999 January-April (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Press service clippings, 1999 May-July (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Press service clippings, 1999 August-December (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Press service clippings-list of articles, 2000-2009 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Press service clippings, 2000 January-May (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Press service clippings, 2000 July-October (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Press service clippings, 2000 November-December (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Press service clippings, 2001 January-July (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Press service clippings, 2001 August-December (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Press service clippings, 2002 January-May (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Press service clippings, 2002 August-October (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Press service clippings, 2002 November (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Press service clippings, 2002 December (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Notebooks listing articles, 1996-2003 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Notebooks listing articles, 1999-2003 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Notebooks listing articles, 1996-2004 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Packets of "non-environmental" newsclippings, 1990-2001 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Topical
    - Scholarship
      - Paul Gorman, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Consumption part 1, 1990-1999 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Consumption part 2, 1990s (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Consumption part 3, 1993–1994 (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - Children's environmental health, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Environmental philosophy, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - Climate change and poverty, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Care for the earth, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - Environmental consequences, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - Cosmos, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - Bhutan, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - Environmental values in American culture, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 18)
      - Religion and spirituality, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 19)
      - Islam and ecology, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 20)
      - Judaism and ecology, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 21)
      - Environmental ethics part 1, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 22)
      - Environmental ethics part 2, 1993–1994 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Additional resources
      - Climate change research, 1990–2005 (Box 38, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence and resolutions on global warming and energy policy, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 25)
      - Key findings by faith group, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 26)
      - Critical Habitat Reform Act, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 27)
      - Faith statements, 1990–1993 (Box 38, Folder 28)
- Audio-Visual Material, 1987-2008; Series IV
  - Produced by NRPE or partners
    - Bridgeport Harbor Power Plant, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      Hi8 MP
    - Caring for Children, Caring for Creation, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      Betacam SP 20 ML
    - Caring for Children, Caring for Creation, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      VHS
    - Caring for Children, Caring for Creation, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      DVD
    - Caring for Creation, no date (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - CCC Training, Tim Wirth Sessions, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      HF 90
    - Conference Film, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Convention Video Segments, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Creation Care Awards, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Earth is the Lord's, no date (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Earth Prayer, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 11)
      Hi8 MP, VHS
    - Endangered, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Endangered Species Act, no date (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Environmental Information Center, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Evangelical Climate Initiative., 2006 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Jewish consultation - photographs (proof sheets), no date (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Mission to Washington - photographs, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - NRPE event - photographs, no date (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - NRPE files back-up on CD, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 19)
      CD-RW
    - NRPE website back-ups on CD and diskettes, no date (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Photographs - miscellaneous, 1987-1990, no date (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Photographs - miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Press Conference, no date; VHS (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Summit for Black Church, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Wall Street Journal, Paul Gorman, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      Zip MAC100
  - Collected resources
    - Among Animals, no date (Box 40, Folder 5)
      Betacam SP 60ML
    - Biblical Call to Earthkeeping, no date (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Black Sea: A Voyage of Healing, no date (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Blessing of the Animals at the Cathedral Church of St. John the Divine, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Blue Planet, no date (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Christians and Climate Change with Sir John Houghton, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Cradled by the Hand of God, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Cry of the Earth, no date (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Demo Reel, no date (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Eating, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Environmental Ethics Curriculum, no date (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Funeral for the Mountains, no date (Box 40, Folder 16)
      VHS, HiMP
    - Getting to the Center of It, no date (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Global Warming/Climate Treaty PSA, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - God's Creation and Global Warming, no date (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Great Warming, no date (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Greening of Religion, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Haddow Communications, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Indiana T.V. Coverage, no date (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Keeping the Earth, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      DVD, VHS
    - Lewisberg United Methodist, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Liberation Spirituality, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Moyers on America, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Network Environment tape 1, no date (Box 41, Folder 11)
      Umatic SP
    - Network Environment tape 2, no date (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Network Environment tape 3, no date (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Network Environment tape 4, no date (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Out of the Air: How Citizens Become Radioactive, no date (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Planet Neighborhood - home, no date (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Planet Neighborhood - work, no date (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Planet Neighborhood - community, no date (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Rehearsing Doomsday, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Restoring Creation for Ecology and Justice, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Sacred Gifts, no date (Box 42, Folder 8)
      Betacam SP 20 ML, VHS
    - Segment on Religion and Commercial Logging in the Pacific Islands, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Spirit and Nature, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Thomas Berry and the Earth Community, 2008 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Wilderness Society, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Untitled, no date (Box 42, Folder 13)